ROJI AWAL

Chyamasing-8, Bhaktapur Cell no.: 9843043399 Date of birth: 8th Jan, 1996

E-mail: rosyawal2068@gmail.com



CAREER OBJECTIVES:

Seeking a position in a leading organization that has a challenging and vibrant working environment where I can utilize my skills and knowledge to the maximum and be challenged to push myself further.

Hardworking and focused Administrative professional offering excellent communication, planning and prioritization skills demonstrated through more than 2 years of performance.

STRENGTHS AND SKILLS

- ➤ Hone my leadership quality by actively participating in social work.
- ➤ Administrative support and business development skills
- ➤ Good interpersonal and communication skills
- > Filing and data archiving
- ➤ Meeting arrangements
- > Customer and client relations
- > Team working and multitasking

WORKING EXPERIENCE

August 2019 - September 2020

Main Office Secretary

English Council Pvt Ltd, Thimi, Bhaktapur

- Recorded new hires, transfers, terminations, changes in job classifications and merit increases to main human resources files.
- Developed recordkeeping systems for employee records and company documents to optimize operations and reduce project lags.
- Assisted with event planning, including associated travel and logistical arrangements.
- Identified and recommended changes to existing processes to improve accuracy, efficiency and quality service.
- Communicated with customers via phone and email to confirm deliveries and respond to inquiries.
- Composed internal memos and external correspondence for senior management and reviewed all documentation to eliminate errors.
- Maintained office supplies inventory by checking stock and ordering new supplies as needed.

June, 2018- July, 2019

Assistant Accountant

Gorkha Eco Construction Pvt Ltd, Challing, Bhaktapur

- Utilized Tally software to analyze, store and record company financial information.
- Reconciled account information and reported figures in general ledger by comparing to bank account statement each month.
- Reconciled company bank, credit card and line of credit accounts every week, investigating and resolving discrepancies to keep accounts audit-ready.
- Managed and responded to all correspondence and inquiries from customers and vendors.
- Presented audit findings to Chief finance officer after reviewing results and paperwork.
- Created detailed expense reports and requests for capital expenditures.

April, 2018- June, 2018

Bank Intern

Everest Bank Ltd, Suryabinayak, Bhaktapur

- Organized company files and created support system to decrease workload and increase productivity of account managers.
- Sorted and organized materials such as physical files, tracking spreadsheets and reports.
- Worked closely with Customer service department to achieve more customer services and increase productivity.
- Completed clerical tasks such as filing, copying and distributing mail.
- Reported back to instructor and management to receive day-to-day tasks and responsibilities.

PARTICIPATIONS AND ACHIEVEMENTS:

- > Participate in Internal audit session in International Green Developers Nepal Pvt Ltd
- Participate in 2 days (Aug 12-13th) Nepal Youth Entrepreneurship Summit 2019
- > Second runner-up in inter-college futsal competition.
- ➤ 1st position in an inter-school cultural dance competition.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

- ➤ Basic knowledge in MS Word, Excel, Outlook and PowerPoint
- > Tally software
- ➤ Good working knowledge of Writing, Speaking and Reading over English and Nepali

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION:

April, 2019- August, 2021

MBA Degree in Entrepreneurship

Westcliff University Presidential Business School, Thapagaun, Kathmandu, Nepal 3.65 GPA

November, 2014- September, 2018

BBA Degree specialization in Finance

Kathmandu Model College (Tribhuvan University) Balkumari, Kathmandu 3.46 CGPA

August, 2012-April, 2014

Intermediate +2 Level in Business Studies

Modern Boarding Higher Secondary School Thimi, Bhaktapur 70.00%

Completed in 2012

SLC

Genuine Secondary School Dekocha, Bhaktapur 77.50%

PERMANENT ADDRESS:

Kamalbinayak-10 Bhaktapur, Nepal Province No: 3

REFERENCE:

Sunita Tha Shrestha

Managing Director English Council Pvt Ltd 9851068846 Naya Thimi, Bhaktapur sunita@englishcounciledu.com

Rajan Duwal

CEO Gorkha Eco Construction Pvt Ltd 9851193194 Mahalaxmi-10, Bhaktapur

razandv	vll@gmail.com		